reflexstock.com 2008-12-20

# Stock Photography: Premium Royalty Free Photos And Rights Managed Images, Illustrations And Vector Art | Reflexstock.com

**Privacy Policy Statement:**

Reflex Stock Limited (“Reflex Stock”) adheres to the following policy about the information that is collected about you (“Privacy Policy”) and is subsequently used and disclosed by Reflex Stock in the course of its normal business activities. This includes but is not limited to the information about you that is collected on the [**www.reflexstock.com**](http://www.reflexstock.com/) web site (the “Web Site”) and during conversations with staff at Reflex Stock.

Any purchase or license by you of any product or service offered by  Reflex Stock or the use of the Web Site signifies your consent and agreement to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy, and to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by  Reflex Stock.

If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, do not acquire or license a product or service offered by  Reflex Stock or use or access the Web Site or information, material, products or services provided therein. If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by Reflex Stock, you may do so by contacting us.

You acknowledge and agree that Reflex Stock may change, alter, amend or update all or any part of the Privacy Policy at any time, and that any such changes, alterations, amendments or replacements shall be effective as of the time of posting of the amended Privacy Policy to the Web Site.

 Reflex Stock will provide notice on the Web Site of any material changes made to the Privacy Policy and your continued acquisition or licensing of products or services offered by  Reflex Stock or your use of the Web Site after the time of posting of such notice will constitute evidence of your acceptance of the changed, altered, amended or replaced Privacy Policy. If at any time you wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by  Reflex Stock, you may do so by contacting  Reflex Stock.

 Reflex Stock may contact you from time to time to notify you of any material changes, alterations, amendments or replacements to all or any part of the Privacy Policy provided that you have given  Reflex Stock your e-mail address and agreed that  Reflex Stock may contact you using that e-mail address.

Collection of Information

When you access and use the Web Site, our web server automatically collects certain information (“Web Information”) about your visit to the Web Site, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, referring IP address, the internet browser and the operating system used by you, and information on what web pages on the Web Site are accessed or used by you. In addition, if you have set up an Account and are signed in, the keywords you use to search for products are collected and may be matched with your Personal Information, as defined below.

If you wish to access and use certain information, material, products and services offered by Reflex Stock, including those offered on or through the Web Site or catalogues published by Reflex Stock,  Reflex Stock will require that you set up an account (“Your Account”) with  Reflex Stock and provide certain information about yourself (“Your Personal Information”).

In setting up your Account, Reflex Stock may require that you provide some or all of the following Personal Information: **_your full name, postal mailing address (including post-code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, username and password_**. In addition to the information above, if you wish to purchase products or services, Reflex Stock will require your credit card number and associated information, or if billing to a purchase order account, any financial information necessary to be approved for account.

 Reflex Stock may also receive and collect information about you from other parties, including the third party vendors featured on the Web Site and from companies that operate a transactional database (see the discussion below in the Use and Disclosure of Information section for a more detailed description of what a transactional database is). The Technical Information and the Personal Information will be used by Reflex Stock for the purposes set out below in the Use and Disclosure of Information section.

Use and Disclosure of Information

 Reflex Stock operates in various jurisdictions around the world and in the course of its business activities will transfer information from one jurisdiction to another between its various operations, suppliers or affiliates.  Reflex Stock and its affiliates may also store and process information in a jurisdiction other than the jurisdiction in which the information was collected. You acknowledge and agree that collected information may be transferred or shared from one jurisdiction to another between  Reflex Stock offices and among affiliates of  Reflex Stock and that such information may be stored and processed by  Reflex Stock and its affiliates in a jurisdiction other than the jurisdiction in which the information is collected.

The information that is collected, stored and processed in the course of its business operations is used for a number of purposes, including processing the transactions you engage in with or through  Reflex Stock, providing customer service to you, communicating with you, informing you of or providing updates or upgrades to products or services, customising and facilitating your use of the Web Site, improving, modifying or developing products and services, and marketing, including direct marketing of products and services offered by or through  Reflex Stock (including those of third parties) through the distribution (by e-mail or otherwise) of brochures, catalogues, advertisements or other publications to you.  Reflex Stock will also use Web and Personal Information about you and aggregate it with Web and Personal Information about others, such that no person is individually identifiable. 

 Reflex Stock will then use this aggregated information for web site analysis, product or service analysis, statistical analysis, or marketing and promotional purposes.

Information about you is important to our business and we are not in the business of selling your information to others. The information that is collected, stored and processed by Reflex Stock will only be disclosed to other parties in the circumstances outlined below.

**Affiliates.** Information will be disclosed to Affiliates as described above. 

**Transactional Databases.** Your Personal Information may be provided to one or more transactional database companies that log your purchase history Reflex Stock work with companies such as Realex.com to provide secure transactional environment for companies to purchase products and service directly from our website and as such your personal information must be shared with them for this purpose. 

**Site analysis.** Your Personal Information may be provided to one or more website analysis companies that log your website activity to help us provide a more rewarding online experience. Such companies monitor your activity on [www.reflexstock.com](http://www.reflexstock.com/) and determine if we can help you in any way and they do so by collecting information about your visit. For this purpose we work with companies like Google.com 

**Third Party Vendors.** Information may be disclosed to the third party providers of products and services.  Reflex Stock has contracted with various third parties to offer their products and services both on or through the Web Site and off the Web Site, and when you buy or license a product or service offered by Reflex Stock, you are generally buying or licensing a product or service from a third party vendor and Reflex Stock is acting as a distributor or reseller. Therefore, in order to process the sale or license of a product or service of a third party vendor offered by or through Reflex Stock and to register you for any technical support or other benefits offered to you by the third party vendor as an owner or user of the product or service, Reflex Stock may disclose Web Information and or Personal Information about you requested by the third party vendor. While Reflex Stock takes precautions in its contracts with third party providers of products and services to protect Web Information and Personal Information about you, Reflex Stock cannot be responsible for the use of such information by such third party providers of products and services and  Reflex Stock strongly recommends that you review the privacy policy of a third party vendor prior to purchasing or licensing a product or service of a third party vendor. You acknowledge and agree that your purchase or license of a product or service of a third party offered by Reflex Stock will constitute evidence of your acceptance and consent that Reflex Stock may disclose Web Information and Personal Information about you to the third party vendor. 

**Agents / Sub-contractors.** Information will be disclosed to a person that Reflex Stock is satisfied has been authorised by you to receive information.  Information will also be disclosed to agents of  Reflex Stock such as companies hired to deliver packages on behalf of  Reflex Stock and a company hired by  Reflex Stock to provide list processing services to assist  Reflex Stock in it’s mailings. Agents / Sub-contractors of  Reflex Stock will only be given access to information required by them in order to perform the services on behalf of  Reflex Stock.

**Disclosure for Legal Purposes.**   Reflex Stock will disclose information about you if required to do so by law, court order or as requested by any other government or law enforcement authority.  Reflex Stock will also disclose information about you where  Reflex Stock, acting reasonably, believes that such disclosure is necessary or advisable, including when  Reflex Stock has reason to believe that the safety of  Reflex Stock employees, customers or others is at risk, or if disclosure of such information is necessary or advisable to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with  Reflex Stock’s rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed in such activities. 

**Debt Collection Agencies.** Information about you will be disclosed to a debt collection agency if funds owing by you to  Reflex Stock are not paid within the agreed upon time or such other time as  Reflex Stock decides is appropriate, acting reasonably. 

**Sale** **of the Business.**   Reflex Stock will disclose information about you to a purchaser in the unlikely event that  Reflex Stock sells all or a part of its business or if  Reflex Stock is acquired by, or merged with, another entity. 

**With Your Consent.** With your prior consent,  Reflex Stock may disclose information about you in situations other than as provided above. 

Warning:  Web Sites beyond our Control

Please note that other web sites may collect information about you when you visit the other web sites and that this Privacy Policy does not extend to information collected by such web sites, including those web sites that provide hypertext links to the Web Site and those web sites not controlled by  Reflex Stock.

Use of Cookies

When you visit the Web Site, we place a “cookie” on the hard drive of your computer to track your visit. The cookie functions similarly to an identification card and allows the Web Site to identify you and to record your passwords and preferences. The cookie allows Reflex Stock to track your visit to the Web Site so that  Reflex Stock can better understand your use of the Web Site and your interest in the goods and services provided therein so that  Reflex Stock can customize and tailor the Web Site to better meet your needs.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. However, on most web browsers you may change this setting to have your web browser either: (1) notify you prior to a web site placing a cookie on your hard drive so that you can decide whether or not to accept the cookie; or (2) automatically prevent the placing of a cookie on your hard drive.  If you choose not to accept the cookies placed on your hard drive by Reflex Stock, you will not be able to access a number of web pages found on the Web Site.

Security

 Reflex Stock endeavours to provide a secure environment in which you can provide and obtain access to information about you.  Reflex Stock has security measures in place to prevent the modification, misuse, loss or misappropriation of information about you, including the provision of a secure environment in which the information is stored and controlling access to such information by parties external to Reflex Stock.

One such security measure used by Reflex Stock is assigning you a user identification and password upon setting up an Account with Reflex Stock. You acknowledge and agree that the user identification provided by  Reflex Stock to you so that you may access, utilize or otherwise enjoy the Web Site and the password selected by and used by you in conjunction with the user identification to access, utilise or otherwise enjoy the Web Site are to be kept secret and confidential. You shall not disclose the user identification or password to any other party without the express written permission of Reflex Stock.

 Changing or Updating Your Information or Your Privacy Preferences

You may view or update all of your information, at any time, which has been stored in your Account, including your privacy preferences, by either logging into your Account on the Web Site and following the appropriate links or by contacting Reflex Stock directly. We ask that you review your Account information on a regular basis to assist Reflex Stock in ensuring that your information remains up-to-date.

Please note that if you do not want your Personal Information to be shared with one or more transactional database companies, you may instruct Reflex Stock not to disclose your Personal Information to such parties by contacting  Reflex Stock as set out below.

Please further note that even if you delete or change your information stored by us, information about you will continue to be stored by us indefinitely and may be used and disclosed by us for the purposes set out under the headings “Affiliates”, “Third Party Vendors”, “Debt Collection Agencies” and “Disclosure for Legal Purposes” under the Use and Disclosure of Information section above. Also, you should note that information may still be stored in places outside of our control.

You may also withdraw your consent to the terms and conditions contained in this privacy policy by providing notice in writing to that effect delivered to the address as specified below. However, please note that if you do withdraw your consent to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, Reflex Stock will, upon receipt, cancel your Account. You further acknowledge and agree that you will not, after withdrawing your consent to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, acquire or license a product or service offered by Reflex Stock (including products or services of third parties) or use or access the Web Site or information, material, products or services provided therein. You may however continue to use products acquired or licensed prior to the cancellation of your Account. If you acquire or license any product or service offered by Reflex Stock (including products or services of third parties) or use the Web Site after withdrawing your consent, such action signifies your consent and agreement to the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy, and to the collection, use and disclosure described herein of your personal information by  Reflex Stock.

Accountability and Complaints

In the event that you have a concern with respect to our collection, use or disclosure of information about you, please forward a statement of concern [info@reflexstock.com](mailto:info@reflexstock.com), we will within 60 (60) days review your written statement and advise you as to the response to your request.

Contact Us

You may contact Reflex Stock Limited on +44 (0) 288 77 89229, or by e-mail at [**info@reflexstock.com**](mailto:info@reflexstock.com)

**Postal Address: Reflex Stock Limited, The Loft Business Centre, 6a Derrycaw Road, Moy, Dungannon, BT71 6NA, United Kingdom**
